Do you want to make a big improvement in your
English?
您想大幅度提高英语水平吗
？
One of the best ways to do that is by mastering
English tenses.
做到这一点的最好方法之一是掌握
英语时态。
This means understanding the difference between
saying "I work" or "I am working", "I have
这意味着要理解
“我工作”或“我正在工作”、“我已经
worked", or "I had worked", and so on.
工作”或“我曾经工作过”等说法之间的区别。
Tenses tell us when something happened, and
whenever you communicate in English, you're
时态告诉我们事情何时发生，
每当你用英语交流时，你都会
using an English tense.
使用英语时态。
The only question is, are you using the right
tense?
唯一的问题是，你使用的
时态正确吗？
In this series, you will learn all of the
English tenses.
在本系列中，您将学习所有
英语时态。
These are full, complete classes for anyone
who wants to speak, write, or understand English
这些都是完整、完整的课程，适合任何
想要更轻松、清晰地说、写或理解英语的人
more easily and clearly.
。
With each tense, we will go step by step from
beginning to end.
每一个时态，我们都会一步步
从头到尾。
We'll also go through the program from beginner
level to the advanced level of tenses.
我们还将学习从
初级到高级时态的课程。
And we'll do lots of practice along the way.
一路上我们会做很多练习。
In addition, I will show you a special way
to understand these tenses, so you can really
此外，我将向您展示一种
理解这些时态的特殊方法，这样您就可以真正
start to use them more easily and quickly.
开始更轻松、更快速地使用它们。
Remember, tenses give structure to the language.
请记住，时态赋予语言结构。
If your structure is weak, your English will
be weak.
如果你的结构很弱，你的英语
就会很弱。
But if your structure is strong, your English
will be strong.
但如果你的结构很强，你的英语
就会很强。
So, join me in this program to master the
English tenses so that you can communicate
所以，加入我这个项目来掌握
英语时态，以便您能够
fluently and confidently in English.
流利、自信地用英语进行交流。